// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Select the most appropriate Antonym for “FUTILE” ",
        answer: "Useful",
        options: [
            "Waste",
            "Expensive",
            "Useful",
            "Cheap"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Select the word occurring in capital letter in the following sentence. His ALLEGANCE to the party was suspect from the very beginning. ",
        answer: "Loyalty",
        options: [
            "Servility",
            "Obedience",
            "Loyalty",
            "Passivity"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "In the Middle Ages there was little progress (P)/ either intellectual or social (Q)/ with the result that (R)/ teaching became the exclusive prerogative of the church (S).Which one of the following is the correct sequence. ",
        answer: "PQRS",
        options: [
            "PQRS",
            "SRPQ",
            "PRSQ",
            "QPRS"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Select the most appropriate One Word Substitute for the phrase “A solution for all difficulties or diseases.",
        answer: "Panacea",
        options: [
            "Altruist",
            "Claustrophobia",
            "Obsolete",
            "Panacea"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Select the most appropriate phrase for the word “Atheist” ",
        answer: "A person who does not believe in God",
        options: [
            "One who denies oneself ordinary bodily pleasure",
            "A person who draws or make maps",
            "One who denies oneself ordinary bodily pleasure",
            "A person who does not believe in God"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "His assignments have taken him to many EXOTIC locations around the world. Select the appropriate antonym of the word in capital letters.",
        answer: "Common",
        options: [
            "Wonderful",
            "Cosmopolitan",
            "Fantastic",
            "Common"
        ]
    },


    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Select the synonym of the word “SALUTARY”",
        answer: "Beneficial",
        options: [
            "Premature",
            "Terrible",
            "Disastrous",
            "Beneficial"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Select the correct option among given ones to fill the blank. The doctor gave me a prescription______________ my cough.",
        answer: "For",
        options: [
            "For",
            "With",
            "At",
            "To"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Choose the correct article to be used to fill the blank. For me, breakfast is___________ best meal of the day.",
        answer: "The",
        options: [
            "A",
            "An",
            "The",
            "None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Find the correctly spelt word.",
        answer: "Adulation",
        options: [
            "Adulation",
            "Adlation",
            "Aduletion",
            "Addulation"
        ]
    },
];